nxpay.com 2010-01-17

# NxPay Client Gateway

**NxPay Privacy Policy**

**Overview**

In order to operate the NxPay service and to reduce the risk of fraud, NxPay ("NxPay" or "we") must ask you to provide us information about yourself and the credit card, debit card, or bank account that you wish to authenticate and validate. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect and how we use that information

NxPay takes the privacy of your personal information very seriously and will use your information only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information or a list of our customers to third parties. However, as described in more detail in Part C below, there are limited circumstances in which some of your information will be shared with third parties, under strict restrictions, so it is important for you to review this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all services that are hosted on the NxPay.com Web site, whether the services are offered by VAT, or by its subsidiaries. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact NxPay.

By accepting the Privacy Policy and User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the NxPay User Agreement. This Privacy Policy will take effect on August 31, 2007. This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 31, 2007

Please note that your personal information will be stored and processed on our computers in Canada. The laws on holding personal data in Canada may be less stringent than the laws of your country but NxPay will hold and transmit your personal information in a safe, confidential and secure environment. If you object to your personal information being transferred or used as described in this Privacy Policy, please do not register for the NxPay service

**Notification of Changes**

This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the NxPay service or as we incorporate suggestions from our customers. If we are going to use or disclose your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time we collected the information, you will have a choice as to whether or not we use or disclose your information in this new manner.

We will post the amended Privacy Policy prominently on our Web site so that you can always review what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check the NxPay Web site at www.NxPay.com at any time for the most current version of our Privacy Policy.

**A Special Note About Children.** Children are not eligible to use our service and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us or use the service. A child's parent or guardian must submit the information for them.

**Required Information.**

To open a NxPay account, you must provide your name, address, phone number, identification number and e-mail address. In order to make payments through NxPay, you must provide credit card, debit card or bank account information. We also ask you to choose two different security questions to answer (such as mother's maiden or your pet's name) This required information is necessary for us to process transactions, issue a new password if you forget or lose your password, protect you against credit card, debit card and checking account fraud, and to contact you should the need arise in administering your account

**Information About You From Third Parties**

In order to protect all our Users against potential fraud, we verify with third parties the information you provide. In the course of such verification, we receive personally identifiable information about you from such services. In particular, if you register a credit or debit card account with NxPay, we will use the card authorization and fraud screening services to verify that your card information and address matches the information that you supplied to NxPay, and that the card has not been reported as lost or stolen.

**Web Site Traffic Information**

Because of the way that World Wide Web communication standards work, when you arrive at or leave the NxPay Web site, we automatically receive the Web address of the site that you came from or are going to. We also collect information on which pages of our Web site you visit while you are on the NxPay site, the type of browser you use and the times you access our Web site. We use this information only to try to understand our customers' preferences better and to manage the load on our servers, so as to improve our service and your experience with NxPay

**Our Use of Cookies**

Cookies are small files of data that reside on your computer and allow us to recognize you as a NxPay customer if you return to the NxPay site using the same computer and browser. We send a "session cookie" to your computer if and when you log in to your NxPay account by entering your NxPay username and password. These cookies allow us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages in our site during the same session, so that you don't need to re-enter your password multiple times. Once you log out or close your browser, these session cookies expire and no longer have any effect.

**Customer Service Correspondence**

If you send us correspondence, we retain such information in the records of your account. We will also retain customer service correspondence and other correspondence from NxPay to you. We retain these records in order to measure and improve our customer service, and to investigate potential fraud and violations of our User Agreement. We may, over time, delete these records if permitted by law.

**Our Use and Disclosure of Information.**

**Internal Uses**

We collect, store and process your personal information on servers located in Canada. We give access to individually identifiable information about our users only to those employees who require it to fulfill customer service requests.

**Disclosure to Other NxPay Customers**

We work with third party merchants to enable them to accept payments from you. Merchants who use this service will share personally identifiable information you provide to them with NxPay in order to validate the information, assess the risks of your payment, or confirm the existence or status of your NxPay account. You permit NxPay to share information with the merchant on the validity of the personally identifiable information you provided to the merchant, and on the existence or status of your NxPay account..

**Disclosure to Third Parties Other Than NxPay Customers**

NxPay will not sell or rent any of your personally identifiable information to third parties. NxPay will not share any of your personally identifiable information with third parties except in the limited circumstances described below, or with your express permission (and with other NxPay customers as described above). These third parties are limited by law or by contract from using the information for secondary purposes beyond the purposes for which the information is shared

1\. We share information with companies that help us process the transactions you request and protect our customers' transactions from fraud, such as sharing your credit or debit card number with a service that screens for lost and stolen card numbers.

2\. We disclose information that we in good faith believe is appropriate to cooperate in investigations of fraud or other illegal activity, or to conduct investigations of violations of our User Agreement. For example, this means that if we conduct a fraud investigation and conclude that one side has engaged in deceptive practices, we can give that person or entity's contact information (but not bank account, credit or debit card information) to victims who request it.

3\. We disclose information in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, levy, attachment, order of a court-appointed receiver or other comparable legal process, including subpoenas from parties in a civil action.

4\. As with any other business, it is possible that NxPay in the future could merge with or be acquired by another company. If such an acquisition occurs, the successor company would have access to the information maintained by NxPay, including customer account information, but would continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy./P>

5\. We share your information with our subsidiaries and joint ventures to help coordinate the services we provide to you, enforce our terms and conditions, and promote trust and safety.

**Our Contacts with NxPay Customers**

We communicate with Users on a regular basis via e-mail to provide requested services, and we also communicate by phone to resolve customer complaints or investigate suspicious transactions. We use your e-mail address to confirm your opening of a NxPay account, to send information about important changes to our products and services, and to send notices and other disclosures required by law. Generally, users cannot opt out of these communications, but they will be primarily informational in nature rather than promotional.

In connection with independent audits of our financial statements and operations, the auditors may seek to contact a sample of our customers to confirm that our records are accurate. However, these auditors cannot use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes

**Internet Address Information**

We use IP addresses, browser types and access times to analyze trends, administer the site, improve site performance and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

**Required Information.**

**Information Security**

NxPay is committed to handling your User information with high standards of information security. Your credit card, debit card and/or bank account information are stored only in encrypted form. We restrict access to your personally identifiable information to employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you

The security of your NxPay account also relies on your protection of your NxPay Activation Code and password. You may not share your NxPay Activation Code and password with anyone. NxPay will never ask you to send your password or other sensitive information to us in an e-mail, though we may ask you to enter this type of information on the NxPay website, which will always have a URL beginning with https://www.NxPay.com/.

Any e-mail or other communication requesting your password, asking you to provide sensitive account information via email, or linking to a website with a URL that does not begin with https://www.NxPay.com should be treated as unauthorized and suspicious and should be reported to NxPay immediately. If you do share your NxPay Activation Code and password with a third party for any reason, including because the third party has promised to provide you additional services, the third party will have access to your account and your personal information, and you may be responsible for actions taken using your password. If you believe someone else has obtained access to your NxPay Activation Code and password, please change it immediately by (i) logging in to your account at www.NxPay.com and changing your User settings, and (ii) contact us right away.

**Accessing and Changing Your Information**

You can review the personal information you provided us and make limited changes to such information at any time by logging in to your account on the NxPay Web site. You can also close your account through the NxPay Web site. If you close your NxPay account, we will mark your account in our database as "Closed," but will keep your account information in our database. This is necessary in order to deter fraud, by ensuring that persons who try to commit fraud will not be able to avoid detection simply by closing their account and opening a new account. However, if you close your account, your personally identifiable information will not be used by us for any further purposes, nor sold or shared with third parties, except as necessary to prevent fraud and assist law enforcement, or as required by law.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, NxPay' information practices, or your dealings with NxPay, you can contact us support@nxpay.com

* * *

### NxPay ACCOUNTHOLDER AGREEMENT TERMS AND CONDITIONS DISCLOSURE STATEMENT

This document contains the rules, regulations, and disclosures that apply to your NxPay Card or NxPay Card account(s). By accepting and using your NxPay Card or NxPay Account you agree that this Cardholder Agreement Terms and Conditions Disclosure Statement shall apply to the use of your Card and account, and you agree to abide by all terms, conditions, and rules set forth herein. Any change or increase in fees will be available on _[www.nxpay.com](http://www.vatproducts.com/)_ web site.

In this Agreement "you" or "your" means the person (persons) who have received the Card or Account and are authorized to use it as provided for in the Agreement and "we" "us" or "our" means Trans Union Credit Union, its processors, assigns or affiliates.

This card is our property and we may revoke the Card at any time without cause or notification. You must surrender a revoked Card and you may not use an expired or revoked card. If your Card is revoked and your Card Account reflects a balance greater than $5.00, we will issue payment of the balance to you at your request, less expenses.

Applicable Federal Law and the rules and regulations of the Federal Reserve Board shall govern this agreement. To the extent that Federal Law is not applicable, the laws of the Province of Ontario shall govern this Agreement. In the event of any conflict between the provisions of this Agreement and any applicable law or regulation, this Agreement shall be deemed modified to the extent necessary to comply with such law or regulation. This Agreement shall be governed by, and construed in accordance with the laws of the State Of Oregon and any proceeding or actions with respect to this Agreement or any services hereunder shall be brought only before a federal or state court in the State of Oregon.

**Use and Purpose of Card:** Your Card is not a credit card. The NxPay Card is a proprietary form of a debit Card. It does not connect in any way to your or any other checking account. You may use it to: (1) withdraw cash at automated teller machines (ATM), (2) pay for purchases at places that have agreed to accept the Card (POS - point of sale), and (3) you may also authorize us to automatically debit or credit your Card to or from third parties by means of pre-authorized EFT (electronic funds transfer) transactions. You may use your Card only to the extent that you have available funds. The funds will be available at any ATM or POS location that bears the Star or other logos as shown on the back of your card. Your current Card balance can be obtained at participating ATM's, through the Internet at _[www.nxpay.com](http://www.vatproducts.com/)_ or by calling 1-800 770-3168. There may be a fee attached to these services,

**How to load your NxPay Card Account:**

ONLINE: you can go online to _[www.nxpay.com](http://www.vatproducts.com/)_ and load funds to your card from a checking or savings account.

Direct Deposit: You can have your employer deposit your payroll funds directly to the card. Simply give your employer the enclosed "Direct Deposit" form and enter your card number where it says account number. You account number acts just like a checking account number.

Participating Retailers: Look for participating retailers that either have the "Speedy Money" symbol and/or was the retailer from which you purchased your card. Always get a receipt from the retail establishment, without a receipt we cannot verify that you gave the merchant any funds to load.

**PIN Confidentiality:**

Do not disclose the PIN or record it on the Card or otherwise make it available to anyone else. You are responsible for the security and use of your Card and PIN. You are liable for any transactions made by a person you authorize or permit to use your Card and/or PIN. The PIN that accompanies your Card is a security feature that functions as your signature, identifying you as the proper user of the Card and authorizing any transactions that you make with the Card. Your PIN allows you to access your funds.

**Amount of Transaction** : There may be additional terms and conditions imposed by the ATM and POS network that will apply to your use of the Card beyond the scope of this Agreement.

**Loss or Theft of The Card:** If you believe that your Card has been lost, stolen or used without your permission, YOU MUST NOTIFY US IMMEDIATELY. Your immediate telephone call to us is the best way to KEEP YOUR POSSIBLE LOSSES TO A MINIMUM. Failure to notify us promptly of the lost, theft, and/or unauthorized use of your Card can result in your loss of any funds associated with the CARD. We are not responsible for any incidental, consequential and/or actual damages as a result of any loss of the Card or funds.

**Authorized Unauthorized or Fraudulent Use:** The Cardholder is responsible for use of the NxPay Card and PIN and is responsible for the full amount of all activity resulting from use of the NxPay Card by any person (including any use of the NxPay Card by persons to whom you have made the NxPay Card or PIN available). The Cardholder is also responsible for the full amount of unauthorized activity resulting from the use of the NxPay Card including due to fraudulent activity or theft of the NxPay Card which occurs before you provide us with actual notification that the NxPay Card has been lost or stolen, provide necessary identification information, and we have been able to "deactivate" the NxPay Card on the Cirrus and Maestro networks.

**No Responsibility for Purchased Goods/Services:** We are not responsible for any failure to supply or lack of suitability or quality of any goods or services purchased from any source using funds transfers authorized through the NxPay Card. You will settle directly between you and the merchant any dispute with respect to any such purchase and any such claim or dispute shall have no effect on the reduction to the Advance Limit carried out when the POS Terminal funds transfer was authorized

**Failure to Complete Transactions:** It is our intent to complete your Card transactions in a timely and efficient manner. However, circumstances beyond our control may result in our inability to complete your transaction in a timely manner. These circumstances include, but are not limited to, the following:

  1. If, through no fault of ours, you do not have enough money in your account to make a transfer;

  2. If the loss is caused by misuse of your Card or PIN in any fashion;

  3. The ATM where you are making a withdrawal does not have enough cash;

  4. The electronic terminal where you are making a transaction does not operate properly;

  5. Natural disaster, fire, flood, and/or communication, system, and/or computer failure;

  6. You report your Card lost/stolen and access to your funds have been blocked by your actions and/or inaction;

  7. A merchant refuses to accept your Card;

  8. A hold is placed on your Card for any reason;

  9. An act of government, police investigation, encumbrance, legal process, and/or court order;

  10. Other unforeseen circumstances not specifically listed above.

**Error Resolution Procedures:** In the event you notify us via telephone of a suspected error, we may require you to confirm the error in writing within ten (10) business days after your verbal submission. It is your responsibility to confirm that we have received your written complaint within the required time period. Your failure to timely send your written confirmation, and/or initially notify us, of the suspected error will result in the loss of your claim.

If you choose, we can send you, upon request, your history in writing. We must hear from you no later than ten (10) days after the transaction in question has occurred. When contacting us please provide:

1.        Your name and NxPay Card account number.

2.        Date and amount of the transaction.

3.        Type of transaction and description of the error. Explain as clearly as possible why you believe it is an error and why you need more information

4.        Dollar amount of the suspected error.

5.        The location and time that the transaction took place

Within ten (10) business days after the receipt of your notification, your claim will be investigated. Our decision to credit your Card for the disputed amount as a result of our preliminary determination does not necessarily entitle you to the funds, as a final determination may not be reached until forty-five (45) days after the receipt of your dispute. Within the forty-five (45) day investigation period, we will either (1) allow the credit for the disputed amount to remain on your Card; (2) credit your Card for the disputed amount, if not already credited; or (3) deny your claim and, if applicable, we will deduct the amount previously applied to your Card. In the event we deny your claim, upon request we will provide you with a written explanation of our final determination.

**Periodic Information:** You are entitled to receive periodic information regarding the use of your Card. Cardholders can choose to receive a copy of the following information.

a)        Card account statements (refer to Cardholder Service Fees schedule)

b)        Amendments to this Agreement, including and without limitation to, any changes in the Cardholder Service Fees set forth therein, or any other terms and/or conditions of your use of the Card; and

c)        All other disclosure notifications and information relating to the Card, as well as the terms of your use of the Card.

**Service Charges:** The unused funds left on the NxPay Card will be reduced by the amount of the current service charges for the services that are arranged through the use of the NxPay Card. In any event, you agree to pay to all relevant service charges (including all transactions imposed by others in connection with the use of NxPay Card). Please see the service charge disclosure for current service charges.

A distribution of ATM Cash advances to you, or POS Terminal funds transfers to merchants/service providers authorized by you, will not be authorized if the remaining funds left on the NxPay Card is not sufficient to cover the ATM cash advances or POS Terminal funds transfers and all applicable service fees.

If a POS Terminal transaction is reversed by a merchant (including, for example, a refund for returned goods), the amount of the reversal shall be added back to the card but any Service Fees previously charged are not reversed. The service charges are subject to change from time to time by notice to the Cardholder or by posting the changes on _[www.nxpay.com](http://www.vatproducts.com/)_. We reserve the right to hold funds.

**Card inactivity and Deactivation:** If your card is inactive for any 60 day period, a fee of $3.00 per month will be assessed until there are no remaining funds on your card. Your card will then be deactivated. This fee is in addition to the monthly fee of $4.00. Your card cannot be reactivated

**Redemption of Unused Funds:** You will have 18 months from the date your Card expires to request a refund of unused funds. To obtain your refund, contact us on our web site _[www.nxpay.com](http://www.vatproducts.com/)_. Upon receipt of your written request, we will refund any unused funds remaining in your account within 30 days.

**Refund Policy:** NxPay will only refund the balance of any funds remaining on an NxPay account. An NxPay account holder can either remove the funds them selves to a bank account, normal fees would apply. Consumers can email customer service nxpay.com and request a check be mailed to them at the registered address on the NxPay system. Customer service will validate the request and will require via email account verification information. A 5.00 check fee will be applied for any requested refunds.

**Discontinuance of Service:** If for any reason we cease to provide NxPay Card services and as a result the NxPay Card is deactivated while the Cardholder still has a positive balance t on the card, then we will either (a) arrange for a new NxPay Card issued by a different supplier to be issued to the Cardholder (subject to compliance with the supplier's card issuance requirements) or (b) advance a cash (or check) payment to the Cardholder for the remaining balance on the card (subject to receipt of identification and return of the old card)

**Non-Insured:** Cardholder acknowledges that this account is not a FDIC insured account. This card is issued by and all funds are held by Trans Union Credit Union for processing only. These are not bank held accounts. You acknowledge and agree your balance is not a deposit, does not bear interest and is not insured by any government agency. You acknowledge and agree that you may only transfer or redeem the value of your balance in accordance with the terms and procedures described in this Agreement and on line at www.nxpay.com.

**Liability:** We will not be liable for any damages (including special, indirect or consequential damages) resulting from any failure, error, malfunction or inaccessibility of any ATM or POS Terminal or any failure, error or delay in providing any ATM cash advances or POS Terminal funds transfers even if we knew that damage was likely or the damage was a result of our negligence or the negligence of our employees, agents or representatives.

You agree to pay for any cost to recover amounts that you owe to us. These costs include legal fees on a solicitor and his own client basis as well as those reasonable counsel fees charged by our legal and collections department. If you fail to pay all costs, we may direct funds available on the card to the payment of such costs.

**Amendment to Agreement:** We may change the provisions of this Agreement and the service charges from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by sending you notice at the last address notified to us or posting a notice online at www.advantcard.com. If we mail a notice, it is considered to be received by you 5 days after it is deposited in the mail. If you use the NxPay Card after we send or post a notice, you are deemed to have accepted the change as of the effective date set out in the notice.

**Funds:** All funds held on the card are subject to exchange rate fluctuations.

**Privacy Disclosure:**

**Confidentiality and Security of Nonpublic Personal Information:**

We restrict access to nonpublic Personal Information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic Personal Information.

**Nonpublic Personal Information We Collect:**

We collect nonpublic Personal Information about you from the following sources:

\- Information we receive from you on applications or other forms  
\- Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others  
\- Information we receiver from a consumer reporting agency

**Nonpublic Personal Information We Disclose:**

We do not disclose, not do we reserve the right to disclose any nonpublic Personal Information about our customers or former customers to anyone except to other nonaffiliated third parties as permitted by law.
